You want to know why Prince Leon was chosen as Pride's fiancé, is that right?
The Kingdom of Anemone does have
a second and a third prince; however...
I spoke with them directly, and thought only Prince Leon seemed suited to her.
The King of Anemone wished for this as well.
That explanation just doesn't add up.
By the way, Stale.
As per your earlier request,
I will allow you to apprentice under Vest
beginning a week from now.
If I'm going to study with Uncle Vest,
I'll have practically no time to be with Pride.
But if that makes me more of a benefit
to Pride and our citizens in the future, then...
I... no longer need to stay by her side.
Every day's unique, you get one chance at it
So you'd better make it count
When people flaunt morality
You've gotta beware they've got their own agenda
Somewhere in your head, there's a voice that's messin' with ya
Don't ever let it turn you 'round
It can't even blow all that hot air it's full of
Get yourself in gear and live however you wanna
Live so fast that the claws of despair will languish in your dust
And you'll be the one with an agenda that they'll all see as just
Keep on shouldering the world around you
Keep on doubting every thought that's bound you
If things go awry, keep pushing through
And know that everything'll work in the end
If you find it's in your power to change the world
I'm sure you can make the future bright
We'll blaze on ahead until we track down the route we want to take
We'll keep trying every door until we find one that goes our way
Stale, are you finished speaking with Mother?
The Cruel Queen Speaks
What's the matter?
I'm just a little tired.
Elder Sister...
She's sleeping?
She said she hardly slept last night.
Last night?
Rest here with us, Stale.
To be honest...
I've been really lonely these past three days.
I felt like Prince Leon had taken my sister away.
But then Pride invited me to the gardens,
and she hugged me with everything she had.
I think she noticed that I was feeling lonely
and did it to comfort me.
But then, she told me...
Stale?
Pride?!
Stale...
I missed you.
She told me that, too.
I've missed you as well.
It's okay, I'll always be here.
Even when we're apart, my heart will always be with you.
Even if I'm not next to you,
even if you fall in love with that man...
I still belong to you, body and soul.
Arthur!
Princess Pride?!
I'm so glad that I didn't miss you passing through!
You've got horrible bags under your eyes! Are you okay?!
I'm sorry!
I surprised you, didn't I?
Uh, no...
I'm sorry!
It's just, um...
I apologize for not speaking with you yesterday.
You forced yourself to escort us
even though you didn't feel well, right?
Princess Pride!
Um...
There's something I want to ask you...
Are...
Are you happy?
I am.
After all, I have you and everyone else with me.
That's good.
So you weren't just grinning and bearing it, then?
Huh?
My apologies, that was rude of m—
Oh, don't be silly!
Arthur?! Are you all right?
Please, let me worry about you.
Why did you have that fake smile inside the carriage?
Why are you putting up a front?
Does he have some sort of dirt on you or something?
Is this all for the country?
Stale, Tiara, and I are all worried about you,
and yet you seem so, so far away...
I'm sorry.
Thank you, Arthur. And you two, as well.
I'm grateful that you worry about me.
However, I'm truly fine.
Okay, it's just as I thought.
No matter how hard this is for her,
she's dead set on taking it on all on her own.
Like she feels it's her destiny to be a lone wolf or something.
I want to...
protect her smile.
I'll be by your side...
Forever.
Thank you.
If the man chosen as her partner is one that she likes,
then I will continue to protect their happiness.
If he turns out not to be the one,
then I will protect Pride from him
and take care of her in his place.
Nothing will change.
Because I've long since dedicated everything to Princess Pride.
Mother, I've had a premonition!
I must go, for the sake of the people!
To our allied nation, the Kingdom of Anemone!
Arthur! Elder Brother!
Arthur, how are you feeling?
Oh, I'm fine!
I'm sorry I made you worry.
Have you heard about your assignment from the Captain?
Yes, I have!
On the day of, well...
I believe I'll be causing you a lot of trouble, but...
I do appreciate your assistance.
Yes, ma'am!
Pride...
What in the world are you going to Anemone to do?
Don't worry.
There's nothing dangerous going on this time.
Then you must have some other reason for going, right?
Well, it's probably nothing.
Just think of it as a visit—
What do you mean by "probably nothing"?
What has you so concerned?
Does it have something to do with
what you've been hiding from us?
Pride.
I'm still powerless, and there's nothing I can do to help.
I'm not even asking to accompany you.
But I can still offer emotional support.
If you won't share because you find us untrustworthy, then so be it.
However...
I doubt that's the case.
Because I know you better than that.
We're willing to believe everything you have to say.
Even if it's merely hypothetical.
And rest assured, none of us will fault you
if things don't turn out as you expect.
If you see fit to trust us, then please tell us what's on your mind.
At least just a little bit.
You are more stunning than even the stars in the sky
when you're bathed in moonlight, Pride.
I think we should come together as one tonight, right here.
Prince Leon.
If you want to be intimate with me,
then I'm fine with that.
We are engaged to be married, after all.
However, that is not what your heart truly desires.
This isn't something our relationship needs.
It's okay, Prince Leon.
You've performed very well these past three days.
Anyone would agree that you had
the demeanor of the perfect fiancé.
What are you saying?
You don't have to perform in front of me.
There is no need to lie to yourself
and pretend there is love here.
I understand completely.
Prince Leon.
Please, make me a promise.
In exchange, I will keep tonight's events to myself,
and return to playing
the happy couple with you tomorrow.
Just who are you?
I am the first-born princess
of the Kingdom of Freesia, Pride Royal Ivy.
I am first in line to the throne,
and I have the special ability of precognition.
I am the only person in this world
who knows your true desires.
Listen, Prince Leon.
You absolutely must not leave your castle
for an entire week after you return to your country.
Not even to check around.
Especially on the last day.
That is when you will lose everything.
The trust of your people and even the king.
Please, keep this promise.
I can't explain now,
but all of this is for what you truly desire.
This is for your happiness.
And so, I gave Prince Leon a warning, but I'm still worried.
If things go wrong, I want to...
What's wrong?!
In short, last night in Prince Leon's room, uh...
you did nothing but talk, and then left?
Yes, that's right.
I'll skip the part about how Leon made a pass at me.
Anyways, I want to—
Okay!
So this top-secret visit is to ensure
that Prince Leon doesn't leave the castle
and realize your premonition, correct?
That's agreeable enough.
In any event, if he really does leave the castle,
we can secretly track him down,
act before he's found
by Anemone's guards, and detain him—
I mean, protect him.
Such disgraceful behavior from Prince Leon
would only be a black mark
on both our kingdom and on Anemone!
Oh, jeez.
I want to set the record straight on some things,
but Stale's tongue is way too sharp!
That's all it was, seriously?
I had imagined so much worse...
U-Um, I'm truly sorry that I worried you!
Ugh, my impression of the situation
was way off the mark.
I even dragged Stale into it.
But that only made you worry about us instead!
Man, how pathetic!
I'm really sorry, Stale.
It's okay.
I think what I told you only made things worse...
See, Elder Sister?
They weren't angry with you at all.
Right.
Thanks, Arthur.
I'm sorry I didn't give you a proper answer
when you asked me before.
You're amazing, Arthur.
You noticed right away that I was having a hard time.
You even said you'd stay by my side.
It made me so happy!
Please promise, Pride,
that you'll rely on us next time.
Whether you need our help or not.
Let us share the burden.
I'm sorry.
It's a bad habit of yours, sister.
You mustn't take on everything on your own.
We're all here for you.
I'm not the only one who will feel awful
watching you suffer all on your own.
All of this is for what you truly desire.
What I desire is...
Leon.
As first-born prince,
you must set an example for your younger brothers
and aim to become a king the people desire.
From a young age, my life revolved around
learning everything that I needed to become king.
But one question popped into my mind...
What makes a "king the people desire"?
Your Royal Highness, Prince Leon!
Prince Leon!
Your Royal Highness!
Your Highness Prince Leon!
Prince Leon!
Crown Prince Leon!
A king who continuously meets the people's desires.
That is the definitive answer.
It was a spiritual awakening for me.
I want to be loved by the people.
I want them to desire me. To covet me.
Not anyone else.
Me.
Those are dangerous thoughts, Brother.
They can be considered "attention-craving",
"narcissistic", and "possessive".
Such labels will harm your good reputation.
I will never forget the shock of hearing
my younger brother's criticism.
I knew I had to dispense with such distasteful emotions,
and temporarily refrained from even leaving the castle.
However... My body and soul still demanded it.
Big Brother.
In that case, why not dedicate yourself to socializing with the members of high society?
I followed my brother's advice and tried to socialize
with the young ladies around my age.
But then I noticed the feelings
those ladies exhibited towards me were...
attention-craving,
narcissism,
and possessiveness.
It frightened me.
I was aghast to have once directed such horrible emotions
towards the very populace I was meant to protect.
In the end, I couldn't provide
any of what they sought from me,
and the rumor that I was a womanizer spread.
What I desire is...
to be prince consort of the Kingdom of Freesia
and thereby bring peace to both of our kingdoms.
As a king, an older brother, and even as a human...
I have proved inadequate.
So this is all I can really do.
Leon.
About your engagement to Princess Pride...
It's possible that we may call the whole thing off.
I'm going to reach out to the Freesian queen
and prince consort again to discuss it further.
I am truly sorry for causing
so much uncertainty in your life.
Here we are, Lady Jeanne and Lord Philip.
We will stand guard after we've carried the luggage inside.
Thank you.
Hopefully, Prince Leon will keep his promise tonight.
And everything will go smoothly with no commotion.
Tomorrow, depending on the conversation between Father and the Queen of Freesia,
my engagement may be called off,
bringing shame to the Kingdom of Anemone.
Or if the engagement stays in place,
despite the disrespect I showed the Kingdom of Freesia,
then I will rarely ever set foot here again.
Ridiculous.
What happiness is there for me in any of this?
Big Brother. Here.
No one will recognize you if you wear this.
Please relax and get out of the castle.
We want your happiness above all else, Brother.
That's right.
My desire right now is...
to leave the castle and mingle with the people.
That's also what my younger brothers desire.
I'm sorry.
I can't do this, not tonight.
Why not, Leon?!
Brother, do you not wish to meet with the people?!
You absolutely must not leave your castle.
Understood, Brother.
But seeing as how we brothers
must sadly part ways soon,
will you allow us one last selfish wish?
Please partake in this gift,
to celebrate your engagement.
Thank you.
Why...
am I here?
The Most Heretical Last Boss Queen:
From Villainess to Savior.
Episode 3: "The Cruel Queen and the Truth".
The Cruel Queen and the Truth